https://www.searchengineprojects.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
HomeServicesFranchise MarketingPay-Per-Click ManagementSearch Engine MarketingSearch Engine OptimizationSocial Media MarketingTranslation & LocalizationVideo EndorsementsWeb Analytics ServicesWebsite DesignWebsite UsabilityPortfolioB2B MarketingContractor MarketingDental MarketingHVAC MarketingJewelry MarketingLaw Firm MarketingPersian Rugs MarketingPharmacy MarketingPlastic Surgery MarketingPlumber MarketingSalon MarketingBlogAbout UsContact Us
Search for:
Search for:
LinkedInFacebookTwitterYelpInstagram
(888) 669-6961
Privacy Policy
Home/Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyInternet Marketing Team2020-01-02T17:03:53-08:00
SearchEngineProjects | Privacy Policy SearchEngineProjects.com is subsidiary of SearchEngineProjects.com and follows its PRIVACY POLICY (Last Updated Januray 1, 2020) SearchEngineProjects.com (“SearchEngineProjects,” “we,” “us” or “our”) operates a Web site located at www.SearchEngineProjects.com (the “Site”) from which users can gather information concerning news and services by SearchEngineProjects (the “SearchEngineProjects Services”).
This SearchEngineProjects Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you access the Site and when you use the SearchEngineProjects Services.
Information Collection and Use:
SearchEngineProjects receives a variety of “personally identifiable information,” including your email address, IP address, and message content. SearchEngineProjects also collects names and mailing addresses (including street, city, state, and zip code) from users providing the information. SearchEngineProjects also requires that you provide your email address on the “Contact us section of the Site so that we are able to respond to your question(s) by email. You have the option of also providing information regarding your name, demographics (such as your state and country of residency), operating system, browser, Internet service provider (“ISP”), connection type and email program that you are using.
SearchEngineProjects also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP Address and the page you requested. Your IP address is not linked to your email address or SearchEngineProjects. In certain areas of this Site, we require that you provide us with personally-identifiable information, in order to be able to use that portion or those portions of this Site. For instance, the names and contact information of persons who visit our Web sites are added to our database so that, for example, they may be contacted in the future regarding SearchEngineProjects’s products, services or future opportunities. Such contact may occur by email, telephone or mail, as SearchEngineProjects deems appropriate. SearchEngineProjects uses your email address for the following purposes:
To contact you about the SearchEngineProjects Services or the Site.
To notify you when you receive a SearchEngineProjects email message.
To communicate with you concerning problems or malfunctions which you report.
Information Sharing and Disclosure:
SearchEngineProjects will not sell or rent your email address, name, mailing address, or other supplied information to anyone. SearchEngineProjects will not share your email address, first or last name, mailing address, or other received information to anyone, except as stated below: We may disclose personally identifiable information about you as legally required in order for us to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes.
Changes to This Privacy Policy:
SearchEngineProjects may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on the Site.
Questions or Suggestions:
If you have questions or suggestions, please send an email to info@SearchEngineProjects.com.
IP Addresses:
When your Web browser or email application requests a Web page from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where the requested information should be sent. This is called your computer’s “IP address.” (IP stands for “Internet Protocol.”) For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up ISP, the IP address may be different every time you log on. Information Collection and Use Practices SearchEngineProjects receives your IP address each time you view a Web page from the Site. Your IP address is not linked to your email address or any other personally identifiable information. Your IP address may be used for various purposes, including: to diagnose service or technology problems reported by you that are associated with your IP address; to estimate the total number of users visiting the Site from specific locales, countries or regions of the world.
Log Files:
When a Web page on the Site is requested, that request (including the date and time) is logged on our servers with information including the IP address of the computer that requested the page. We use log files for debugging and troubleshooting purposes. IP addresses and access times are not linked to your email address or any other personally identifiable information.
Data Storage/User Information:
All SearchEngineProjects account information (including names, mailing addresses) and content of email messages are stored on multiple redundant disk storage systems. No removable offline copies or backups are made. If you request deletion of your email address or any other identifiable information, your information will be deactivated and removed from our user registration database within 30 days. In reviewing the information above, please keep in mind that SearchEngineProjects cannot and does not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including other Site users, including the manner in which they might use information received either from SearchEngineProjects or independently.
Category: Internet Marketing Firm
Toggle Sliding Bar Area
Close
Font Resize
A-
A+
Keyboard navigation
Underline links
Website Usability
Search Engine Projects uses cookies on our site. By clicking accept or continuing to use our website, you are agreeing to our use of cookies in accordance with our Privacy Policy.OkPrivacy policy
Go to Top
